Online Privacy Policy

Last update: December 2020

• Applicability

• Modifications

• Collection and Use of Your Information (including via Cookies)

• Sharing of Your Information

• Third Party Sites

• Security of Personal Information

• Children's Information (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act)

The BNY Mellon Charitable Gift Fund (the “Gift Fund”) is a nonprofit organization incorporated in the State

of Delaware and recognized by the Internal Revenue Service (the “IRS”) as a tax-exempt public charity under

Sections1 501(c)(3), 509(a)(1), and 170(b)(1)(A)(vi) of the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 (the “Code”) and a

“sponsoring organization” that administers donor-advised funds described in Section 4966 of the Code.

The Gift Fund appreciates your concerns about the privacy of personal information that you provide to us

through this website (“Site”). Accordingly, we have posted this Online Privacy Statement to explain how we

handle such information.

Applicability

If you do not agree to the terms of this Online Privacy Statement, please do not provide us with any

information and do not use the Site. By using the Site and voluntarily providing your personally identifiable

information to us, you consent to the collection and use of such personally identifiable information as set forth

in this Online Privacy Statement. This Online Privacy Statement applies to this Site. Our online programs may

have different Online Privacy Statements. To view the Online Privacy Statement for specific programs please

click on the Privacy link on that site.

Modifications

This Privacy Statement is effective as of the date listed above. We may modify this Online Privacy Statement

at any time so please check from time to time for such modifications. Any changes to this Online Privacy

Statement will be effective as of the date they are posted. If you have specific questions regarding this Online

Privacy Statement or any information you have sent via the Site, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Collection and Use of Your Information (including via

Cookies)

We use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies (called "Cookies" in this Online Privacy Statement) to

track information provided to us by your browser and by our software application when you use the Site. A

cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on the web browser on your device and can later

retrieve. "Session" Cookies are temporary and will expire at the end of a browser session; that is, when you

leave a website. Session Cookies allow a website to recognize you and carry information as you navigate

between pages during a single browser session and allow you to use the website most efficiently. "Persistent”

Cookies, in contrast, remain in the Cookie file of your browser even after you leave a website and after the

browser is closed. They enable a website to recognize you upon your return, remember your preferences and

provide tailored services to you. A cookie will not contain information that will enable us to contact you via

telephone, e-mail, or other means.

We, and third-party service providers acting on our behalf, use session and persistent Cookies to:

• Remember preferences that you submit as well as those generated from your usage data

and your responses to polls and surveys on our Site;

• Measure your use of our Site in an effort to improve its quality and enhance your overall

experience, including tracking page views, time and date of Site access, and other usage

data, and identifying your operating system and browser type (but not other information

about your computer or the programs on it) and your general geographic location;

• Measure the effectiveness of our programs and campaigns; and

• Allow you to share certain information on our Site via social media bookmarking buttons,

email or on social networking sites.

The third-party service providers mentioned above use any personal information they collect on our behalf

solely for the purpose of providing the contracted service to us. They have also agreed to confidentiality

restrictions.

Most browsers are initially set to accept Cookies. However, you have the ability to change your browser

settings. It may also be possible to configure your browser settings to enable acceptance of specific Cookies or

to notify you each time a new Cookie is about to be stored on your device enabling you to decide whether to

accept or reject the Cookie. You can also disable Cookies by configuring your browser setting to reject

Cookies. Please refer to the help section of your browser for instructions on disabling Cookies. For more

information about Cookies, how they work, why they are so useful and how to disable them, you can visit

www.allaboutcookies.org.

If you do not wish to accept Cookies from this Site, please either disable them or refrain from using this Site. If

Cookies are disabled, it may mean that you experience reduced functionality or will be prevented from using

all or part of this Site.

We may use aggregated usage data to track trends and analyze patterns on the Site. You may also voluntarily

submit information, including by responding to our online polls and surveys, requesting information from us,

or asking to be contacted by one of our representatives. If you work for one of our institutional donors, we may

obtain your business contact information from your organization. If you register to enter an area of this Site,

the Site will recognize who you are and collect all information that you submit (including subscription to

emails, etc.). Any information collected about you from this Site may be associated with other identifying

information that we have about you.

In addition to the above uses, we may use your information for the purpose of administering your donor

advised fund account and providing information we believe may be of interest to you. The information

collected also is used to provide a record of communications between the Gift Fund and its Site visitors and to

comply with any applicable legal and/or regulatory requirements.

Sharing of Your Information

We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. We share your information only

with our (i) service providers that have agreed to confidentiality restrictions and use any personal information

they collect on our behalf solely for the purpose of providing the contracted service to us; (ii) as otherwise

described herein in order to provide you with our programs and services; and (iii) to comply with all applicable

laws, regulations and rules, and requests of law enforcement, regulatory and other governmental agencies.

Also, we may share in aggregate, statistical form, non-personal information regarding the visitors to the Site,

traffic patterns, and Site usage with our partners.

Your information will be transferred and stored in jurisdictions, including the United States and other

jurisdictions that may be subject to differing standards of data protection requirements. the Gift Fund will take

appropriate steps to ensure that transfers of personally identifiable information are in accordance with

applicable law.

Third Party Sites

This Site may contain links to third party sites (including social media bookmarking buttons that enable you to

share certain content on our Site). Please review the cookie and privacy statements of these third-party sites to

understand how they may use Cookies and your information. Our Online Privacy Statement does not apply to

your use of a third-party site.

Security of Personal Information

We utilize reasonable security technologies to protect sensitive information. However, the security of this

information depends in part on the security of the computer you use to communicate with us, the security you

use to protect User IDs and passwords, and the security provided by your internet access services provider. We

are not responsible for the security of your internet access services provider; you should review the security

and privacy policies of your internet access services provider carefully. Information that you access via this

Site may be stored on your computer during your session for your convenience. If others have access to your

computer or your User ID and password, they may be able to access this information. We are not responsible

for the security or privacy of information communicated to or from such a computer. Finally, you should keep

any correspondence you receive relating to this Site or the Services (including, but not limited to registration

information, emails, or any other information) confidential and in a safe place.

Children's Information (Children’s Online Privacy

Protection Act)

We respect the privacy of your children and do not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable

information from children under the age of 13 through this Site.

This Online Privacy Statement was last updated on the date listed at the top.

Terms of Use

Use and Acceptance

This website (the "Site"), and any tools and/or services (including but not limited information, data, reports,

research papers and articles) offered and/or provided by the \ Gift Fund and/or its partners (referred to

collectively as “we” or “us”) through this Site (collectively, the "Services"), are offered to you conditioned

upon your acceptance without modification of these Terms of Use. By using this Site or any Services, you

agree to these Terms of Use. Please read these Terms of Use carefully. If you do not agree to these Terms of

Use, you may not use this Site or any Services offered or provided through this Site.

Modification

We may change these Terms of Use from time to time without notice to you. You should review these Terms

of Use each time you use this Site or a Service to make sure you agree to them. By using this Site or Services

or engaging in any of the activities described in these Terms of Use after changes have been made to these

Terms of Use, you are agreeing to accept and comply with those changes.

Authorized Use; Copyrights and Trademarks

This Site and the Services may contain copyrighted works and trademarks and other proprietary material

owned by us or our content providers. You may use the information available from this Site for informational

purposes only. You may print copies of pages from this Site for your personal purposes, provided that each

copy includes any copyright, trademark or service mark notice or attribution as they appear, on the pages

copied. The availability of third-party data from or through this Site is not to be used as a substitute for a

license or services agreement directly with the relevant content provider. Except as stated above, you may not

copy, reproduce, publish, post, transmit, display, store, sublicense, transfer or distribute material or images

from this Site without our express written permission or that of our content providers, as applicable

("Permission"). You may not modify, alter, revise, paraphrase, omit, or change any material or images on or

from this Site without Permission. You may not create derivative works, whether based in whole or in part

upon the information on this Site or any portion thereof without Permission. You may not modify, amend,

reduce the size of or in any way obscure any warning, notice, liability limitation or other license provision in

material or images on or from this Site. Nothing contained on this Site and/or the Services should be construed

as granting, by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license or right in and to our trademarks or copyrighted

material. The information contained in this Site is subject to change without notice.

We reserve the right to prohibit access to anyone whom we determine are violating these Terms of Use,

restricting or inhibiting any other user from using or enjoying the Site, or whose conduct we reasonably

determine may constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any applicable

local, state, national, or international law.

Limited Availability, Eligibility

Not all features mentioned on this Site may be available in all geographic areas. Your eligibility for particular

feature is subject to final determination by us and/or the applicable content provider.

Limitation of Liability

BY ACCESSING THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO WAIVE ALL CLAIMS AGAINST US AND ALL THIRD

PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS REGARDING THIS SITE, THE INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THIS

SITE AND ANY INFORMATION RECEIVED BY YOU AS A RESULT OF USING THE SITE, AND ANY

USE BY YOU OF SUCH INFORMATION. YOU AGREE THAT UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL

WE OR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING, OR DELIVERING THIS SITE

OR ITS CONTENTS OR SERVICES BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT

NOT LIMITED TO, ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL

DAMAGES OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOOD WILL, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, USE,

DATA, EQUIPMENT OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF

THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES) THAT RESULT FROM (1) THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO

USE THIS SITE OR ANY SERVICES; (2) THE CONSEQUENCES OF ANY DECISION MADE OR

ACTION OR NON-ACTION TAKEN BY YOU OR BY ANYONE TO WHOM YOU COMMUNICATE

SUCH INFORMATION, OR FOR ANY ERRORS BY YOU IN COMMUNICATING SUCH

INFORMATION; (3) THE COST OF SUBSTITUTE SERVICES; OR (4) ANY OTHER MATTER

RELATING TO THE CONTENT, SERVICES, OR DISTRIBUTION OF SERVICES THROUGH THIS

SITE. WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGE OR INJURY TO PERSONS OR PROPERTY

ARISING FROM ANY USE OF ANY PRODUCT, INFORMATION, PROCEDURE, OR SERVICE

OBTAINED THROUGH THIS SITE.

OUR ENTIRE LIABILITY AND YOUR EXCLUSIVE REMEDY FOR ANY DISPUTE OR CLAIM

RELATED TO THESE TERMS OF USE, THE SITE, ANY SERVICES, OR THE PRIVACY POLICY IS

YOUR CESSATION OF THE USE OF THIS SITE AND ANY AND ALL SERVICES. BECAUSE SOME

JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR

CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, IN SUCH JURISDICTIONS LIABILITY IS LIMITED

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

WE CANNOT AND WILL NOT ASSUME ANY LIABILITY FOR UNAUTHORIZED OR FRAUDULENT

USE OF THIS SITE AND ANY SERVICES.

Indemnification

YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY AND HOLD US AND OUR THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS

HARMLESS FROM ANY LOSS, INCLUDING REASONABLE ATTORNEYS' FEES, RELATED TO ANY

COST, DAMAGES, CLAIM OR EXPENSE RELATED TO ANY CONTENT YOU SUBMIT, POST TO OR

TRANSMIT THROUGH THIS SITE, YOUR USE OF THE SITE OR THE SERVICES, YOUR

CONNECTION TO THE SITE, YOUR VIOLATION OF THESE TERMS OF USE, OR ANY HARM YOU

CAUSE ANOTHER USER.

Disclaimers

SOME OF THE CONTENT ON THIS SITE OR THE SERVICES MAY BE PROVIDED BY THIRD

PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS AND USERS. WE ARE A DISTRIBUTOR AND NOT A PUBLISHER

OF SUCH CONTENT AND HAVE NO CONTROL OVER IT. ANY OPINIONS, ADVICE, STATEMENTS,

SERVICES, OFFERS OR OTHER INFORMATION GIVEN OR PROVIDED BY THIRD PARTIES

(INCLUDING MERCHANTS AND LICENSORS) ARE THOSE OF THE RESPECTIVE AUTHORS OF

SUCH CONTENT AND NOT OURS.

ALTHOUGH WE USE REASONABLE EFFORTS TO PROVIDE ACCURATE AND UP-TO-DATE

INFORMATION THROUGH THIS SITE, WE AND THE CONTENT PROVIDERS MAKE NO

WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS AS TO THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR

COMPREHENSIVENESS OF CONTENT ON THIS SITE AND ANY SERVICE. THE INFORMATION

CONTAINED ON THIS SITE AND ANY SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" "AS AVAILABLE"

BASIS. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF

ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH REGARD TO INFORMATION CONTAINED

ON THIS SITE AND ANY SERVICE, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF

MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. WE

AND THE CONTENT PROVIDERS CANNOT AND DO NOT GUARANTEE OR WARRANT THAT THE

FILES AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOADING FROM THIS SITE AND ANY SERVICE WILL BE FREE

FROM INFECTIONS OR VIRUSES, WORMS, TROJAN HORSES, OR OTHER CODE WITH

CONTAMINATING OR DESTRUCTIVE PROPERTIES. YOU HEREBY AGREE TO RELEASE AND

HOLD US HARMLESS FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, LOSSES, EXPENSES OR DAMAGES

RELATING TO ANY DISCLAIMED WARRANTY DESCRIBED IN THIS PARAGRAPH.

THE INFORMATION PROVIDED IN ANY SERVICE OR IN THIS SITE IS NOT INVESTMENT OR

LEGAL ADVICE. INFORMATION RECEIVED VIA THIS SITE OR THE SERVICES SHOULD NOT BE

RELIED UPON FOR PERSONAL, LEGAL OR FINANCIAL DECISIONS AND YOU SHOULD

CONSULT AN APPROPRIATE PROFESSIONAL FOR SPECIFIC ADVICE TAILORED TO YOUR

SITUATION.

Severability

If a court determines that any Term of Use is illegal or unenforceable, then such term will be eliminated and

the remaining Terms of Use will remain in force and effect.

Entire Agreement; Jurisdiction and Choice of Law and Forum

These Terms of Use constitute your entire agreement with us regarding this Site and any Services, and

supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written

between you and us with respect to the Site or the Services. This Site and/or the Services may not comply with

legal requirements of foreign countries, therefore the Site, its contents and the Services are intended only for

access and use by United States residents and are presented solely as a service to visitors and/or subscribers

located in the United States of America and its territories. These Terms of Use are governed by and construed

in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of

law. You expressly and irrevocably agree that exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any claim or dispute with

us, our employees, contractors, officers, directors and content providers or relating in any way to your use of

this Site or the Services resides in the state or federal courts in New York City, New York and you further

irrevocably agree and expressly and irrevocably consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in those courts

over any action brought under these Terms of Use. We and you hereby waive the right of trial by jury in any

action arising out of or related to the Site, Services, or these Terms of Use.

Submissions

You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself when you elect to

provide personal information to us. You also agree to maintain and promptly update any such information to

keep it accurate. Other than information addressed under our Online Privacy Policy, any and all comments,

suggestions, ideas, graphics, or other information that you transmit or post to the Site becomes and will remain

our property and may be used by us anywhere, anytime and for any reason whatsoever. Except as may be

provided in the Online Privacy Policy, any information or materials submitted to us will be treated as non-

confidential and non-proprietary, and we will not have any obligation to use or evaluate any information we

receive from you. We will not have to pay you or anyone else for using any ideas or other materials that you

may transmit to or post on the Site.

Links To Other Websites

This Site provides links to other websites that we think might be of interest to our users ("Linked Sites").

Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may be moving to another provider's website. These

Linked Sites and their providers are not controlled by us, and we are not responsible for the contents or the

proper operation of any Linked Site. The inclusion of any link does not imply our endorsement. We encourage

you to read the terms of use and privacy statements of these Linked Sites as their policies may differ from ours.

Protecting Your Information

We utilize reasonable security technologies to protect sensitive information.

BNY Mellon is licensed under the following U.S., Patents: 5,940,510; 5,949,880; 6,105,013; and 6,237,095.
